Good ideas arrive while you're moving, then disappear inside a long voice note.
Nugget starts with one tap: capture first, organize later.
The voice-first screen stays deliberately simple. I can speak naturally, watch the live waveform, and stop when the thought is out of my head.
The recording is saved in this browser before cloud processing begins. From here, Nugget can transcribe the audio, organize the transcript, and return a reviewable result without losing the original source.
For this interface walkthrough, I'm switching to a clearly disclosed, preprocessed safe capture. One ramble has become three separate nugget drafts.
Each draft is editable before I trust it: title, summary, category, tags, purpose, goals, blockers, research needs, and next actions. Explicit, inferred, and suggested labels show how every field relates to the source.
This next view is Nugget's labeled local sample library, so it does not make a new GPT-5.6 call.
I can search locally, filter by category and tags, and switch between a balanced card feed and a compact scan view.
Opening an idea puts the useful summary first. The purpose, concrete goal, blocker, research need, and suggested action stay together, while editing and source details remain one tap away.
Accepted next steps collect in Actions without losing the idea they came from. That turns a useful thought into something I can actually move forward.
Nugget keeps saved recordings and ideas in the browser. After explicit consent, transcript text is treated as untrusted input and sent to GPT-5.6 Terra for source-grounded separation and organization. Structured results are validated before review.
Settings also shows live Whisper and GPT-5.6 Terra health.
Codex helped plan, build, test, debug, and verify the product; I made the product and release decisions.
Nugget makes moving thoughts useful.