Good ideas arrive while you're moving, then disappear inside a long voice note.
Nugget starts with one tap: capture first, organize later.
The voice-first screen stays deliberately simple. I can speak naturally, watch the live waveform, and stop when the thought is out of my head.
The recording is saved in this browser before cloud processing begins. Nugget can transcribe the audio, organize the transcript, and return a reviewable result without losing the source.
For this interface walkthrough, I'm switching to a clearly disclosed, preprocessed safe capture. One ramble has become three separate idea drafts.
Each draft is editable before I trust it: title, summary, category, tags, goals, blockers, research needs, and next actions. Grounding labels show how every field relates to the source.
Confirmed ideas become a searchable local library. This view uses Nugget's labeled sample data, so it does not make a new GPT call.
Opening an idea keeps its summary, category, tags, goals, blockers, research, and next actions together instead of burying the useful parts back inside a transcript.
I captured this feature idea in Nugget itself. That saved thought became what you're seeing now.
Work with this idea can explore a thought, create a plan, or prepare a grounded brief for another AI. The source transcript stays off unless I explicitly include it.
I confirm exactly what is sent, then GPT-5.6 gets to work.
The result is a structured, editable brief with an objective, context, assumptions, constraints, deliverables, and success criteria. It stays grounded in the organized idea, labels missing context instead of inventing it, and produces a prompt I can copy or download.
Settings keeps the privacy boundary visible and reports live Whisper and GPT-5.6 Terra health.
Nugget captures ideas and helps bring them into the real world.